

## ABOUT ME

I'am 20 years old. I'm studying software development at UADE and Full Stack development at Soy Henry, Also increasing my knowledge in courses related to programming.

I seek to develop and grow in the technological field and obtain knowledge in survey and implementation of solutions for different customers.

## CONTACT

- (54) 11 6460-2560
- jjulian.contrerass@gmail.com
- www.linkedin.com/in/juliancontre raslucero
- github.com/julcontrerass

## EDUCATION

- -2nd year in software development at UADE currently
- -Full Stack Developer in soy henry 2023

### PORTFOLIO



# TECH SKILLS

#### JAVASCRIPT Y TYPESCRIPT

FRONTEND

Html5 Css3 Aiax

React Js React Native Redux BACKEND

NodeJs Sequelize Express Testing BASES DE DATOS

MongoDB PostgreSQL

### SOFT SKILLS

- -Adaptability
- -Curiosity
- -Dedication
- -Empathy
- -Problem solving
- -Negotiation
- -Cooperation

### WORK EXPERIENCE

## Diaper acuarela

ENE 2021 - JUL 2021

- Seller
- Repositor
- Deliveryman

## Sportclub belgrano

JUL 2021 - FEB 2022

- Receptionist
- Closing and cash control
- Administration

### Sportclub obras paraguay

ABRIL 2022 - DIC 2022

- Receptionist
- Closing and cash control
- Administration

### LENGUAGES

- -Spanish
- -English A1